FWD has been taking how people feel
about insurance and turning it on its
head but now we are adding how it sounds
not only are we empowering our customers
with digital human-centric tools and
services we are also ensuring that this
customer-led approach helps people
across Asia to celebrate living their
way so what should they hear when they
press play at FWD we are committed in
enabling every customer we Inspire to
celebrate living lives without
hesitation or audio branding
demonstrates our energy toward changing
the way people feel about insurance and
to provide customer even more way to
connect with us emotionally to
encapsulate our brand into a new audio
identity we engage Universal music group
and Elias to guide us through the
process the first step in our process is
Discovery through brand immersion we
discovered that the pieces should ladder
up to the brand Promise by being
Innovative joyous and fun once the
discovery phase was complete and a Sonic
brief was crafted to Define her
strategic audio goals we then moved into
musical development we start by pulling
sounds into an audio mood board so that
we can start to determine what sounds
are working best we ultimately realized
that version one felt the most on brand
with our sound established we then
created additional audio pieces and
versions for our various brand needs our
intent is to ensure our Sonic branding
is applied across all our communication
and consumer touch points these include
both offline and online platforms such
as our websites apps films and various
brand interaction with us
we hope this helps us to strengthen
familiarity and enrich engagement with
our brand every time they see us and now
hear us we are excited to share this new
audio identity with the rest of the
world but more importantly we are
honored to be the insurance provider for
so many people as they celebrate living
[Music]